{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","address":"19725 Strasburg","zipcode":"48205","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"035257","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/29/2016","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"210.0","geom":"0101000020E610000070D6ACD5ECBF54C008A524C861384540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44537","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","inspectionDate":"2018-12-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"139","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44537","inspectionDate":"12/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"44537","inspectionDate":"12/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-12-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"}]},{"inspectionid":"42563","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","inspectionDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42563","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"20 foot candles","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"42563","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"42563","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"STEAM TABLE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40872","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","inspectionDate":"2017-11-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40872","inspectionDate":"11/14/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Freezer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"37256","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","inspectionDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37256","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"37256","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"38944","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","inspectionDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38944","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily readable","subProblem":"","location":"THERMOMETER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"38944","inspectionDate":"4/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"42277","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","inspectionDate":"2016-11-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42277","inspectionDate":"11/1/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"42277","inspectionDate":"11/1/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1171"}}